Having faith is like Wi-Fi you can always connect to.
And so that's why you always got to pay the bill.
It can't just be something you turn on when you need it.
Yes, it can't be something that you turn on when you need it.
And I think that Wi-Fi doesn't work everywhere.
This belief system does.
And I hope that the damage that historically Christianity has done in the West.
And I do want people to know that Western Christianity and the teachings of Jesus Christ are not necessarily synonymous.
That right there, that's like a part two.
They're not synonymous.
You should do a whole masterclass.
That statement is very, that's a strong statement.
Because it's those same people who are here in the West using the teachings of Jesus to try to undermine the people that are his kin as well.
From the Middle East.
And again, the origin of Christianity was the Middle East.
Ba-dum-pum!